(Howard:)...with indestructible
Kryptonian perspiration.
Booyah.
(Sheldon:)Superman would have taken his uniform
to a Kandorian dry-cleaner...
(Sheldon:)...before he left the bottle.
Kandorian dry-cl...? I give up. You can't have
a rational argument with this man.
(Howard:)Hey, isn't that the guy who won
the MacArthur genius grant last year?
(Howard:)No, not all at once.
- Then how?
- Leonard.
(Howard:)Now Raj.
(Howard:)Now Sheldon.
- I didn't get a good look. Can I go again?
- No.
- That's David Underhill. So what?
- So what?
(Sheldon:)His observation of high-energy positrons
has provided the first evidence...
(Sheldon:)...for the existence
of galactic dark matter.
(Leonard:)I have two words for you.
The first is "big," the other's "whoop."
It is a big whoop. Made almost all the work
you've done completely useless.